vibescaster.com 2016-08-25

# Privacy | Vibescaster

### Registration

You can use Vibescaster without registering. If you want Vibescaster to remember your settings permanently or if you want to access your personal page from more than one PC you need to register with your email address and a password. In addition this will also protect your account from unauthorized access. When you register we'll send you a welcome email.  
We may send you service announcements and advertising messages from YOUniversal Next Limited or third parties.  
You can unsubscribe from these announcements and advertising messages at any time by sending an email to [info@youniversalnext.com](mailto:info@youniversalnext.com)

### Policy Privacy

Vibescaster.com is operated by YOUniversal Next Limited.

YOUniversal Next Limited, we respect the privacy of our users and the importance of the information they entrust to us. We summarize below the basic information policies and practices in place on the Vibescaster.com website.

### Information we may collect

We may collect information that can identify you ("personal information"), such as your name and email address, (i) when you (or other users) provide it to us.

We also may collect other types of information in the following ways when you visit Vibescaster.com website:

  * Our server logs automatically collect information, such as your IP address, your browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us track users' movements around our site and understand trends.
  * We may assign your computer one or more cookies which may collect information to facilitate access to our website and to personalize your online experience.
  * We may use standard Internet tools, such web beacons, which collect information that tracks your use of our website and enables us to customize our services and advertisements.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Should we ever do so, we will comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.

### Information others may collect

We may allow third-party advertising companies or ad networks to display advertisements on our websites.

  * We do not provide any personal information to these companies.
  * These companies may use tracking tools, such as cookies, to collect information about computers used to view or interact with their advertisements.
  * Some of these companies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers consumers the ability to opt out of ad targeting by all member companies.

### How we may use information we collect

We may use information to:

  * Fulfill your requests for products and services;
  * Offer products and services that may be of interest to you;
  * Process payment for products or services you order via Vibescaster;
  * Customize the advertising and content that you see on our website;
  * Facilitate use of our Vibescaster website;
  * Manage your account and your preferences;
  * Analyze use of and improve our website, products and services;
  * Identify and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of our website;
  * Enforce any EULA, terms of use, terms of service or other terms/policies governing your use of the Vibescaster website.

### With whom we may share information we collect

We will not share your personal information with others except as indicated below, or except when we inform you in advance and give you the opportunity to opt out. We may share personal information with:

  * Service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf;
  * Other YOUniversal Next Limited businesses;
  * Other businesses with which we partner or which we carefully select to offer you products, services, and promotions through our Vibescaster website; and
  * Other third parties in limited circumstances, such as complying with legal requirements, preventing fraud, and protecting the safety of our users.

We may share aggregated, non-personal information in any of the above situations and also with advertisers and others.

### Your choices

You may choose:

  * Not to provide personal information, although that may result in your inability to obtain certain services or use certain features of our Vibescaster website;
  * To stop receiving promotional emails or newsletters from us by sending an email to the contact address at the bottom of this policy or by modifying your email and information sharing preferences;
  * To delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings, although if you do so, some of the features or services of the Vibescaster website may not function properly;
  * To review and update your personal information by contacting us at the email address below or, if you have an online account on our website, by logging into that account

### Security

We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. If we make material changes in the way we collect, use, or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an email and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Vibescaster website.

### How to contact us

If you have any questions about this summary, our Privacy Policy, or our information practices, please contact us by email: [info@youniversalnext.com](mailto:info@youniversalnext.com)

This website uses cookies, also third parties cookies, in order to send to you adverts and services in line with your preferences. If you are willing to know more about cookies or to deny your consent to all or to certain cookies, please click here.. By closing this banner, scrolling this page or clicking any element whatsoever on this page you consent to the use of cookies.  OK
